Kyoka?
镜花…
Now we have the brain that controls the Red Strings.
如此一来 操纵红色系线的大脑就到手了
I'm sorry, Kasane.
对不起 重…
I think they are here to welcome us.
看似是在欢迎我们
But why?
但为什么呢
I think they know why Yuito and us are here.
他们好像知道结人和我们的事
I don't see anything
在能看到的范围里
within my range of sight.
没看到可疑的东西和人
However,
不过…
there are places I can't see.
也有许多地方 无法透视
Tsugumi, let me know if you spot anything.
鸫 发现异状时 就通知我
Leave it to me.
交给我吧
Wataru, I'm counting on you too.
渡 也拜托你了
The system Major General Fubuki gave us is functioning normally.
吹雪连队长准备的系统 也没问题
Please stay cautious.
大家小心点喔
Sure.
好
SCARLET NEXUS
《绯红结系》
♫A crime in reality♫
现实的Crime
♫For Heaven's sake♫
For Heaven's sake
♫Accepts any fake♫
接受虚假
♫And disappears piling the eternity in fantasy♫
永恒的幻想 层层逝去
♫Won't take it at all, I get sick♫
绝非完美 I get sick
♫A girl looking back♫
转身而来的少女
♫Casts the miracle into the instant world♫
在这瞬息世界中 落下了奇迹
♫Did you lie♫
Did you lie
♫Spit the venom♫
Spit the venom
♫I know why♫
I know why
♫I've found a game of ecstasy♫
找到了 绝顶的游戏
♫Red Criminal gets life♫
Red Criminal gets life
♫I've never been in love♫
I've never been in love
♫Don’t know when I started getting sick of this world♫
我何时开始厌倦了这样的世界
♫We will fly♫
We will fly
♫Someday I won't be crying♫
Someday I won't be crying
♫I've been sacrificing myself not to hurt anybody♫
为了不再伤害 而牺牲了自己
THE MOON'S SECRETS
(月球的秘密)
May I ask,
请问…
what is this place?
这是什么地方
Please communicate with the history.
请与历史对话
The Moon will protect you.
月球会守护着各位的
Communicate? With whom?
对话 跟谁对话啊
There is no one else here except us.
除了我们 没有别人了
Do they want us to read the book?
是要我们读那本书吗
Well, Tsugumi?
鸫 如何
I don't detect anything suspicious.
没有特别可疑的地方
Be careful.
小心点
What is it that you seek?
你们在寻求什么
-Kyoka? -What is going on here?
-镜花 -这是怎么回事
Why is it showing Kyoka's image?
为何会是镜花的影像
Name: Kyoka. Matched files: one.
人名 镜花 符合的资料有一件
Answering a question regarding Kyoka Eden.
回答关于镜花伊登的问题
Kyoka Eden.
镜花伊登
She is one of the design children created by Togetsu.
是渡月制作的设计孩童
Design? Created?
设计 制作的
I had heard rumors about design children.
设计孩童 我曾听过相关传闻
I think they were created through a specific genetic combinations
我记得是经过特定的遗传因子组合
to have a certain physical appearance, strength, and brain power.
设计成拥有任何外在特征 及身体脑力的人类
Am I right?
对吧
I found some information as well.
我这里也查到了
Luka's explanation is pretty much on point.
跟鲁卡说得差不多
It's viable theoretically,
但虽理论上可行
but it just can't work practically.
可实际上却行不通
So Kyoka was a design child?
镜花是设计孩童吗
Kyoka Eden.
镜花伊登
A brain power researcher.
是以超脑力研究者
She was created with Professor Hitoyo Pope's cells.
一夜波普博士的细胞制作而成的
Professor Pope is an expert in the field of brain power.
博士是脑学科领域的专家
She is also the founder of Togetsu Faith.
也是渡月教的教祖
They share the same look.
相同的长相
Did Professor Pope make Kyoka?
是波普博士 制作镜花的吗
No. Professor Pope died about 2000 years ago.
不 波普博士在2000年前逝世
She is no longer of this world.
早已不在这世上了
She said 2000 years ago.
2000年前
That was about the same time New Himuka was founded.
跟新日向建国时期相同
Maybe they have information about New Himuka from that time period.
这里是否也有 当时新日向的情报
If we dig around, we might find some dirt on the government too.
只要好好调查 或许能找到政府隐瞒的情报
What was New Himuka like when it was first founded?
刚建国的新日向 是什么样的国家
Answering a question regarding the founding history of New Himuka.
回答关于新日向建国的历史概要
New Himuka was founded 2020 years ago.
新日向是距今2020年前
It was a country founded by the people from the Ark.
由方舟队的居民建立的国家
The Ark? What is that?
方舟队 那是什么
It's the name of the immigrant group that moved to Earth from the Moon.
从月球降落到地球的 移民团名称
They came from the Moon?
从月球
Yes.
是的
Humans originally lived on Earth.
最初 人类原本在地球上繁衍
But 300 years ago,
然而 追溯到3000年前
the Earth's orbit underwent a drastic change.
由于地球的轨道产生变化
The catastrophe laid waste to Earth.
造成环境巨变
Human population was greatly reduced.
人口也大幅减少
For the sake of human's continuity,
为了种族存续
they moved to the Moon and built their new home.
人类移民到月球上生活 建造都市
They tried to change Earth's environment from the Moon.
从月球表面改善地球的环境
What are you talking about?
妳… 妳说什么啊
After 1000 years of effort, the rehabilitation project came to an end.
经过1000年 改善计划来到末期
Earth's condition was improved to a certain degree.
地球环境调整到某个程度
The Moon government sent immigrants back to Earth.
月面政府派遣移民团到地球
Those were people from the Ark.
那就是 方舟队
This is only getting more confusing.
越说越搞不清楚了
Humans moved from Earth to the Moon,
人类 从地球移民到月球
and then they returned to Earth?
再从月球降落地球吗
This is hard to believe.
竟然有这种事
The immigrants from the Moon...
月球派遣而来的移民团
That means only a certain group of people were sent here.
意思是 选出一部分的人类到地球
Yes.
没错
Are there still people living on the Moon?
现在 月球上有人类吗
I do not have a clear answer to that question.
关于这个问题 无法明确回答
Why?
为什么
The communication with the Moon government has been completely cut off.
现在 与月面政府通信管道 全被阻断了
Cut off...
阻断…
I get it now. It must be the Extinction Belt.
我知道了 是断绝之带的缘故吧
Yes.
是的
Due to the interference from the Extinction Belt,
由于断绝之带造成的影响
we have no way to know the condition on the Moon.
现在 无法从地球知道月球的状况
But if the Extinction Belt was there,
可是 既然有断绝之带
how did the immigrants get here?
移民团又如何抵达地球的
The Extinction Belt didn't exist back then.
当时 还不存在断绝之带
The Extinction Belt only appeared
移民团降落地球之后
after the people came down to Earth.
才出现断绝之带吗
Yes, that is correct.
是的 没错
From what I know about history,
我学到的历史是
the Extinction Belt only appeared after the Spring of Extinction.
断绝之带 是因断绝之春才出现的
The Spring of Extinction happened during the founding era.
而断绝之春 是建国时期发生的事
So the Others and the Extinction belt showed up around the same time?
怪异 和断绝之带是同时出现的吗
No, the Others came some time
不 断绝之带出现后
after the Extinction Belt appeared.
过了一阵子 才突然出现的
They didn't appear together?
不是同时出现的
But the Others came from the Extinction Belt.
可是 怪异来自断绝之带啊
What do you make of this?
你觉得呢
This is a little hard to believe.
令人难以置信
The Others...
怪异…
What exactly are the Others?
怪异究竟是什么
I do not possess the information
关于这个问题
to answer that question.
此处没有你要的情报
You require access to BABE.
需要进入贝比
BABE?
贝比
Is there another system similar to this?
还有其他类似的系统吗
We got information Suoh and Seiran government don't have.
虽然得到在苏芳 和青蓝都没有的情报
I gave up halfway through the explanation.
听到一半 我已经放弃理解了
The information is simply unbelievable.
内容太过荒唐
We should only take it as a verbal legend passed down in Togetsu.
只能当作渡月口耳相传的传说吧
Maybe it's part of the Togetsu Faith's scripture.
是不是渡月教教典中的一小节啊
If the immigrants founded New Himuka...
如果是移民团建造了新日向
So our founding father, Yakumo Sumeragi, came from the Moon too.
建国之父 八云皇也来自月球啰
It's just as the hologram said.
如果影像说的是真的
It's not just Yuito, but the whole human population on Earth.
不只是结人 而是所有地球人
We are all descendants of the immigrants from the Moon.
都是来自月球的移民后代啰
That can't be real.
怎么可能
I know.
就是啊
Try asking something else.
问问其他事情吧
Please tell us what you know about the Kunad Gate.
请告诉我们 关于岐之门的情报
A question regarding the Kunad Gate.
回答关于岐之门的问题
Kunad Gate: A black hole that appeared above the Kunad Highway.
岐之门 出现在岐高速运输公路的 疑似黑洞的现象
It's gravitational pull is abnormal and still growing.
其重力异常状态 日以俱增
It will consume the whole planet soon.
在不久的将来 便会吞噬地球
Due to Yuito Sumeragi's brain power,
并且 受结人皇的超脑力影响
the Kunad Gate is still growing.
岐之门正逐渐扩大中
Earth's total destruction is inevitable.
地球的灭亡 已是无可避免的事
How is Yuito part of this?
为何会提到结人
However, you need not fear.
不过 无需恐慌
Place your faith in Togetsu,
只要相信渡月教
everyone will be granted salvation.
所有人终将得到救赎
The Moon will protect all of you.
月球会守护众人的
Wait! How is my power affecting the Kunad Gate?
等等 我的超脑力怎么了
What does it have to do with me?
岐之门跟我有什么关系吗
The Kunad Gate is correcting trivial matters
岐之门 将矫正琐碎问题
and bringing the flawed universe back to the right path.
并调整错误的宇宙
It's the very phenomenon that will bring the righteous future.
实现正确未来之物
The souls marching toward death
迈向死亡的灵魂
will return to the Moon.
将回归月球之母
Yuito, don't be concerned about the story.
结人 你别在意那些内容
But the Kunad Gate is indeed consuming its surrounding.
岐之门 确实吸走了周遭的东西
Will it grow to the point where it consumes Earth?
它会越变越大 最后吞噬地球吗
We shouldn't believe those stories.
这些话不能过于相信
Yes. It might be a trap.
对 搞不好是陷阱
We mustn't be tricked.
不要被他们唬弄了
You have a point.
说的也是
So, what shall we do next?
接下来 该怎么办
I'm concerned with the system named BABE.
我很在意影像说的"贝比"
When we asked her about the Others,
问她关于怪异的问题
she said we'd require access to BABE.
她说需要进入"贝比"
Do you seek the knowledge of BABE?
各位想得到关于"贝比"的知识吗
What is BABE?
"贝比"是什么
It's the city computer that manages Togetsu.
管理渡月的都市计算机
So it functions like Suoh's Arahabaki.
就是苏芳的荒吐神吗
Togetsu has a management system too?
渡月也有啊
I'll lead the way, please follow me.
我为各位带路 这边请
Kasane, answer me!
重 快回答
Arashi? Kagero?
岚 阳炎
We fell for Kyoka's trick.
被镜花大姊 摆了一道吗
Please answer me! Kyoka! Shiden!
拜托 镜花 紫电 快回话
What happened to everyone?
大家到底怎么了
I'll be right back.
我去去就回
The memories we share
跟你们在一起的时间
will not perish.
不会就此消逝
There are two brains controlling the Red Strings.
操纵红色系线的大脑有两个
We'll reach our goal very soon.
就快得到我们渴求的成就了
Huh?
咦
Shiden, aren't you coming with us?
紫电不跟来吗
Kasane, you still lack the resolve.
看来重妳还没做好觉悟
We are just the same.
而我们也是
Thank you.
谢谢
I'm doing this to correct this flawed world.
这都是为了矫正错误的宇宙
Sorry, but I need to borrow this.
抱歉 借我用一下喔
Yuito and Tsugumi...
结人 鸫
Kasane...
重…
Who is it?
谁
Someone is beckoning me.
谁在叫我
Kasane, congratulations. You're finally awake.
重 恭喜妳 妳终于苏醒了
Kasane...
重…
Look.
妳看
The puppy is small like you are.
跟重一样的小狗喔
Look at it barking. Don't you find it adorable?
牠在汪汪叫呢 可爱吧
A puppy?
小狗
I feel this nostalgia, but why?
为何 这么怀念
I know this person.
我知道…这个人
It was killed.
被杀了
Yes, I remember.
对 我记得
My precious friend was murdered right before me.
我最重要的朋友 在我面前…
The data is the same.
数值没什么变动
That didn't trigger her brain power.
没发动超脑力
Killing her beloved animal doesn't bring enough stimuli to her.
杀死玩伴小动物 还不足以给予刺激…
That's enough!
够了
Stop hurting this poor child's soul!
别再…别再伤害重的幼小心灵了
Is this really for the sake of our future?
这么做 真的是为了未来吗
She is a Design Child created for this exact purpose.
她是为此诞生的设计孩童
She is unlike the failure you are.
跟失败的妳不同
For the sake of correcting this universe,
为了矫正错误的宇宙
to secure the real future,
取回正确的未来
we need the Red Strings.
我们需要红色系线
Is there a need to do so?
真的有矫正的必要吗
Mother. It was so warm and gentle.
妈妈 既温暖又温柔
She was always trying to protect me.
总是保护着我的人
But I lost the memories.
而我 却忘了…
Is there a need to correct the world?
真的有矫正的必要吗
The world is great as it is now!
世界就这样也很好啊
No, what is this sensation?
不要…这是什么感觉
I don't want to remember this.
我不想想起来
The outcome of your failed education is beyond disappointing.
教育失败竟退步至此
We only assigned you as her caretaker so you'd have something to do.
为了让妳有点事做 而让妳照顾她…
Yes. That's enough.
是啊 已经够了
We'll proceed with her.
接下来就用她吧
Yes.
对…
Is that so?
是吗…
So you...
你们果然…
All of you...
这些家伙…
My mother was...
把妈妈…
Kasane, I'm sorry.
重 对不起
I wish you a great future.
希望 妳拥有幸福的未来
Yes.
对
I lost my caretaker that very day.
那天…我失去了照顾我的人
I lost my mother.
我失去了妈妈
I was created as a brain power user.
我是 被创造出来的超脑力者
The power of the Red Strings...
这股力量 红色系线
Where am I?
这里是…
The memories I forgot.
曾忘却的记忆
I...
我…
Kasane.
重…
Stop hurting this poor child's soul!
别再…别再伤害重的幼小心灵了
Mother...
妈妈…
CONTACT LOST
(无法联络)
Damn it!
可恶
You can stop trying now, Shiden.
你也差不多该放弃了吧
What?
什么
You're too noisy, I can't sleep.
吵死了 妨碍我睡觉
How can you still sleep in this situation?
这种状况妳还睡得着
Panicking won't do us any good.
慌也没用
We should rest while we can.
能休息的时候就尽量休息
You should get some sleep too.
你也睡一下吧
As if I can sleep!
谁睡得着啊
Kyoka.
镜花
Even you...
妳也…
Lady Kasane, we brought you new clothes.
重大人 我带了新的衣服
-What is it? -Verify it now.
-怎么了 -快确认
Wait, it's me.
等等 是我啦
Kagero.
阳炎
The dashing prince is here to save his princess.
王子来解救被困住的公主
My lady, please don't punch me in the face.
公主可别把王子揍飞喔
You left the team before we even entered Togetsu.
在我们进入渡月前 你就脱队了
Did you know?
难道你当时就…
If I were in cahoot with Kyoka,
妳想说我跟镜花串通好的
why would I come here to rescue you?
那我干嘛来救妳呢
Calm down and think.
冷静下来好好思考吧
I told you so, didn't I?
我不是说了
You'd regret coming to Togetsu.
来渡月的话会后悔的
I'll explain everything to you later.
我之后再跟妳说明
This place has become far worse after I left.
渡月比我以前在的时候 糟很多
I think they got their hands on something.
而且他们好像抓到了什么
Yuito and his team are here too.
结人他们也来了
Yuito is here too? This is bad.
结人也来了 那就糟了
Togetsu is after my Red Strings.
渡月的目标是我的红色系线
Yuito probably has the same power as mine.
八成也对拥有相同力量的结人…
I thought as much.
我想也是
It seems I have no choice but to save them too.
看来 也得去救他们了
Let's get moving.
动作快
Lady Kasane isn't here.
重大人不在
Kasane went missing?
重不见了
It's not fun to meet the people
见到渡月的家伙们
from Togetsu.
一点也不有趣
Well, that's it for me.
好啦 就是这样
Hey! Come back!
喂 等等
Kagero...
阳炎…
Kasane! Kagero!
重 阳炎
Thank goodness you two are safe.
太好了 你们没事吧
Haruka, where is Arashi and the team?
遥 岚他们呢
I don't know, I can't contact them.
不知道 连络不到他们
You knew they'd be captured.
你知道他们被抓到哪吗
What a shame.
很可惜…
I know where Yuito is.
知道结人他们要去的地方了
Master Yuito, this is the place.
结人大人 就是这里
BABE will answer all of your questions.
贝比会回答您所有的问题
Master Yuito, I'm sure you want to know whether the information was true or falsified.
结人大人定想知道 所听到的情报是否为真
A conversation with BABE will clear your doubts.
只要与贝比对话 必定能解除您的疑惑
Please, verify it yourself.
请您 好好确认吧
The Moon will protect you.
月球会守护您的
This is too suspicious no matter how you see it.
不管怎么想 都很可疑吧
We wouldn't let any outsider gain access to the mainframe of Arahabaki.
通常 不会允许外人 进入如荒吐神等级的系统
This is too baffling.
太令人匪夷所思了
Why would a religious group need this powerful computer?
这么小的教团 需要像荒吐神等级的计算机吗
Wataru, can you hear me?
渡…听得到吗
No, we lost the psynet connection.
不行 连不上超脑网络
We must leave at once as soon as we get the information.
调查完需要的情报后 尽快离开吧
Yes.
好
What? Isn't some hologram going to show up?
奇怪 这里不会出现任何人吗
What's going on?
怎么回事
ALERT
(警告)
This feeling...
这种感觉…
It feels like the connection to SAS!
跟连结SAS的感觉一样
Yuito...
结人
This is bad.
糟糕…
I can't move my body.
身体…无法动弹
♫I don't need to let fate dictate me♫
无须被命运所指使
♫Because I believe that I can rewrite it♫
相信定会被改写
♫I'll always be a dreamer now and forever♫
让我们今后 继续做着梦
♫Another sunrise shines now and it blacks out♫
朝阳正光辉灿烂 随后落下
♫What's waiting for us at the world's end♫
在世界的尽头 究竟等着什么
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going♫
未来 灯火永恒不灭
♫Who can shake us♫
谁在威胁我们
♫Who can define us♫
谁为我们决定
♫It's nothing less than our story♫
这是属于我们的故事
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going in your heart♫
未来 你心中的灯火永恒不灭
DESIGN CHILDREN
(设计孩童)